tampaelectric.com 2019-03-08

# Privacy Policy Statement - TECO Energy

##### What you should know:

For each visitor within TECO Energy's Web sites, our Web server automatically recognizes the visitor's domain name. We also collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail; aggregate information on what pages visitors access; and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

#####  How We Use the Information We Collect

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web site, to notify visitors who request it about updates to our site, and may be used to contact visitors for marketing purposes, and to alert you on updated information and services. We also use the information you voluntarily provide to fulfill your request, help you quickly find and/or receive information about TECO Energy, Inc. or one of its affiliated companies, provide more complete service and answer your questions. We do not share customer-specific information with other organizations. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders or requests they have placed online.

#####  Security

Given the nature of the Internet and the fact that no security system is perfect, TECO Energy cannot promise that the information you provide will never be obtained by unauthorized persons. TECO Energy does, however, utilize industry-standard practices to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration and destruction. Such measures include using firewalls and security layers to protect certain sensitive transmissions of information. In some areas of our Web site, we require a user ID and password for you to access certain information. TECO Energy will not disclose such passwords to third parties; however, you are responsible for maintaining the privacy and security of your password.

#####  Links to Non-TECO Energy Site

For the convenience of our users, this site contains links to Web sites owned by third parties. Often, but not always, you can tell that you have linked to a non-TECO Energy Web site because the Web site will open a separate browser window. Links by TECO Energy to such external Web sites do not imply endorsement by TECO Energy of that company, its site or its privacy policy. TECO Energy is not responsible for the content of any linked sites and makes no representations regarding the content or accuracy of materials on such sites. If you decide to visit any third-party sites using links from this Web site, you do so at your own risk.

#####  Children's Privacy Policy

This site contains energy-related facts and information that could be of educational interest to children. TECO Energy does not gather personal information online from or about children. We encourage all children to seek consent of their parents or guardian before providing any information, in any form, about themselves or their household to anyone on the Internet. 

#####  A Special Note for Parents on Children's Privacy Policy

TECO Energy closely scrutinizes its marketing and public information efforts, including this site, to conform to the guidelines put forth by the Children's Advertising Review Unit and the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998\. We encourage you to monitor your children's online time. We further ask that you help us protect their privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information on any Web site without your permission.

#####  Changes to Our Privacy Policy

TECO Energy reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If we decide to change our policy regarding privacy, we will post the revised privacy policy on our site. You may want to visit this site periodically to review the current privacy policy. Use of our site after the posting of a revised privacy policy constitutes your agreement with the revised policy. This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

#####  How to Contact Us:

Our postal address is:  
P.O. Box 111  
Tampa, FL 33601-0111

We can be reached via [e-mail](mailto:tecoenergy@tecoenergy.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).
